Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - R
        - Robinson, Smokey - Great songs and performances that inspired the Motown 25th anniversary television special, 1983; SR-29651; Robinson, Smokey; Miracles (Box 415)
          Catalog # 5316ML; A-side Matrix # 5316ML-A-ISA
        - Robinson, Smokey - A quiet storm, 1975; SR-29652; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          Catalog # T6-337S1; A-side Matrix # T6-337-S1-E5RS-7538-1-REI-03B #13
          Tamla
        - Robinson, Smokey - Get ready, 1979; SR-29653; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          Catalog # M 00027 D1; A-side Matrix # M00027D1-A-65532-D-18A
        - Robinson, Smokey - Yes it's you lady, 1982; SR-29654; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29655. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 6001TL; A-side Matrix # 6001TL-A 15A F1 S-13 ZQA #13 B1Q
        - Robinson, Smokey - Yes it's you lady, 1982; SR-29655; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29654. 2 copies.
        - Robinson, Smokey - Tell me tomorrow; Right in the middle (of falling in love), 1981; SR-29656; Robinson, Smokey; Lavette, Bettye (Box 415)
          Catalog # PR-92; A-side Matrix # PR-92A-66493D 15B FY S-13 ZRZ #13 BIT
        - Robinson, Smokey - Touch the sky, 1983; SR-29657; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          Catalog # 6030TL; A-side Matrix # 6030 TL-A 15D#13 BMJ (T)
        - Robinson, Smokey - Blame it on love and all the great hits, 1983; SR-29658; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          Catalog # 6064TL; A-side Matrix # 6064 TLA 15-A
        - Robinson, Smokey - Theme from big time, 1977; SR-29659; Robinson, Smokey (Box 415)
          Catalog # PR-29; A-side Matrix # PR-29-64192-D-13A BC
        - Robinson, Smokey - Smokey Robinson & Marvin Gaye's greatest hits (Disc one), 1987; SR-29668; Robinson, Smokey; Gaye, Marivin (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29669; SR-29670. Triple album.
          Catalog # SE-10533; A-side Matrix # SE-10533-1-A-2
          Silver Eagle Records, Inc.
        - Robinson, Smokey - Smokey Robinson & Marvin Gaye's greatest hits (Disc two), 1987; SR-29669; Robinson, Smokey; Gaye, Marivin (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29668; SR-29670. Triple album.
          Catalog # SE-10533; A-side Matrix # SE-10533-2-A
        - Robinson, Smokey - Smokey Robinson & Marvin Gaye's greatest hits (Disc three), 1987; SR-29670; Robinson, Smokey; Gaye, Marivin (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29668; SR-29669. Triple album.
          Catalog # SE-10533; A-side Matrix # SE-10533-3-A
        - Robinson, Tom - Now Martin's gone, 1982; SR-29660; Robinson, Tom (Box 415)
          Catalog # SP70960; A-side Matrix # AMSP 070960-A RE-I T2
        - Robinson, Vicki Sue - Trust in me; Don't try to win me back again, 1978; SR-29661; Robinson, Vicki Sue (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29662. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # JD-11228; A-side Matrix # PD-11228 A-1
        - Robinson, Vicki Sue - Trust in me; Don't try to win me back again, 1978; SR-29662; Robinson, Vicki Sue (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29661. Different discs.
          Catalog # PD-11228; A-side Matrix # PD-11228 A-1
        - Robinson, Vicki Sue - Summertime fun; Admit it, 1982; SR-29663; Robinson, Vicki Sue (Box 415)
          Catalog # PRD-32002 DJ; A-side Matrix # PRD-32002 A- DJ -1 45RPM
          Promise Records
        - Robinson, Vicki Sue - Nightime fantasy; Feels so good it must be wrong, 1979; SR-29664; Robinson, Vicki Sue (Box 415)
          Catalog # PD-11442; A-side Matrix # PD-11442 A-1
        - Robinson, Wanda - Me and a friend, 1973; SR-29665; Robinson, Wanda (Box 415)
          Catalog # PLP-37; A-side Matrix # PLP-37-A 10-4 4-73
          Perception Records
        - Robotnick, Alexander - Problèmes d'amour, 1985; SR-29666; Robotnick, Alexander (Box 415)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2316; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2316-SH1 B-21304-SH1 SLM 9744 1-1
        - Robe - Turn on the moon, 1987; SR-29667; Robe (Box 415)
          Catalog # 2000AD-ST4; A-side Matrix # 2000AD-ST-4 A S-18074 REI 1-1
          2000 AD Records
          can't find
        - R.O.C. - Dedicated to my girl, 1992; SR-29672; R.O.C. (Box 415)
          Catalog # 72392 75309-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 75309-1 A RE-I 1-2
        - R.O.C. - 4 richer or poorer, 1999; SR-29673; R.O.C. (Box 415)
          Catalog # CAS 47444; A-side Matrix # XSS 47444 A
          So So Def
        - Roc Project - Never (past tense), 2003; SR-29674; Roc Project; Tina Arena (Box 415)
          Catalog # TB-2404-0P; A-side Matrix # TB 2404 0A
        - Rocca - Le hip-hop mon royaume, 1996; SR-29675; Rocca (Box 415)
          Catalog # ARS 0007; A-side Matrix # ARS 0006A DFI965 6343 A
          Arsenal Records
        - Rocca, John - Move, 1987; SR-29676; Rocca, John (Box 415)
          Catalog # CR12-015; A-side Matrix # CR 12 015 A F/W
        - Rochell, Megan - The one you need, 2006; SR-29677; Rochell, Megan; Fabolous (Box 415)
          Catalog # B0006473-11; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16515-1A RT
        - Rock & Gee - Mellow, 1987; SR-29678; Rock & Gee (Box 415)
          Catalog # TR-520825; A-side Matrix # TR-520 825-A
          Hunsar Records
          Fort Lee, New Jersey
        - Rock-A-Funk-A-Billy (Gallon) - Looking for some action, 1984; SR-29679; Rock-A-Funk-A-Billy (Gallon) (Box 415)
          Catalog # SH-32031; A-side Matrix # VID-290-A PA 1084 G
          Sugar Hill Records
        - Rock, Bon - Junior wants to play, 1982; SR-29680; Rock, Bon; Cotton Candy (Box 416)
          Catalog # TB822; A-side Matrix # TB 822 -I SMK
        - Rock Candy - I got love, 1982; SR-29681; Rock Candy (Box 416)
          Catalog # PRO-7009; A-side Matrix # PRO-7009A -1
        - Rock, Charlie - She's my baby love, 1986; SR-29682; Rock, Charlie (Box 416)
          Catalog # NP 50048; A-side Matrix # NP-50048-A
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - Rock, Chris - Roll with the new (Disc one), 1997; SR-29683; Rock, Chris (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29684. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A2-5026; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-5026-DRM-A-GL1 -1A
          Dreamworks Records
        - Rock, Chris - Roll with the new (Disc two), 1997; SR-29684; Rock, Chris (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29683. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A2-5026; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-5026-DRM-C-GL1 -1A
        - Rock Master Scott And The Dynamic Three - The roof is on fire, 1985; SR-29685; Rock Master Scott And The Dynamic Three (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29686. Different discs.
          Catalog # D-239; A-side Matrix # D 239 A
          Reality
        - Rock Master Scott And The Dynamic Three - Request line; The roof is on fire, 1984; SR-29686; Rock Master Scott And The Dynamic Three (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29685. Different discs.
          Catalog # D-230; A-side Matrix # D 230 A
        - Pete Rock & C.L. Smooth - Take you there; Get on the mic, 1994; SR-29687; Pete Rock & C.L. Smooth; Rock, Pete (Box 416)
          Catalog # ED 5706; A-side Matrix # ST-ED 5706-1-A 1-1
        - Rock, Pete - The yearn, 1996; SR-29688; Rock, Pete; The Lost Boyz (Box 416)
          Catalog # ED 5844; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5844-A3
        - Rock Squad - Facts of life, 1985; SR-29689; Rock Squad (Box 416)
          Catalog # TB 855; A-side Matrix # TB-855-A-RE
        - Rock Steady Crew - Used to wish I could break with Rock Steady, 2000; SR-29690; Rock Steady Crew (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29691. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BS 01; A-side Matrix # BS-01-A ROCK STEADY MC
          Backspin Productions
        - Rock Steady Crew - Used to wish I could break with Rock Steady, 2000; SR-29691; Rock Steady Crew (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29690. 2 copies.
        - Rock Steady Crew - Ready for battle, 1984; SR-29692; Rock Steady Crew (Box 416)
          Signed
          Catalog # RSCLP 1; A-side Matrix # MX204399 RSCLP1 -1
          Australia
        - Rock Steady Crew - She's fresh, 1984; SR-29693; Rock Steady Crew (Box 416)
          Catalog # RSC 312; A-side Matrix # RSC 312 A-1U-1-1-2
          Charisma
        - Rock Steady Crew - She's fresh, 1984; SR-29694; Rock Steady Crew (Box 416)
        - Rock, Tony - Street resident, 1989; SR-29695; Rock, Tony (Box 416)
          Catalog # E-704; A-side Matrix # E-704-A IN GOD WE TRUST MF
          Effect Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Rockers Hi-Fi - 90° fuzzwalk, 1996; SR-29696; Rockers Hi-Fi (Box 416)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8617; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8617-A-SRI
        - Rockers Hi-Fi - Rockers to rockers (Disc one), 1995; SR-29697; Rockers Hi-Fi (Box 416)
          . Double album.
          Catalog # BRLPD 615; A-side Matrix # BRLP 615-A-1
        - Rockers Revenge - Walking on sunshine, 1991; SR-29698; Rockers Revenge (Box 416)
          Catalog # WAR-801; A-side Matrix # WAR 801 A-Re F/W CSB
          Warlock Classics
        - Rockers Revenge - The harder they come, 1982; SR-29699; Rockers Revenge; Calvin, Donnie (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29700. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SWRL 2207; A-side Matrix # SWRL 2207 A RE3
          Streetwise
        - Rockers Revenge - The harder they come, 1982; SR-29700; Rockers Revenge; Calvin, Donnie (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29699. 2 copies.
        - Rockwell - Carmé, 1986; SR-29701; Rockwell (Box 416)
          Catalog # PR-184; A-side Matrix # PR 184-A-67544-15A ZBI #1B
        - Rockwell - Somebody's watching me, 1983; SR-29702; Rockwell (Box 416)
          Catalog # 4515MG; A-side Matrix # 4515MG-A-66949-D-15A
        - Rod - Shake it up (do the boogaloo), 1980; SR-29703; Rod (Box 416)
          Catalog # PRL D 601; A-side Matrix # PRLD 601 A-1G
        - Rod - Shake it up (do the boogaloo), 1988; SR-29704; Rod (Box 416)
          Catalog # PAL-7222; A-side Matrix # TD B-1 PAL-7222-A1
          Atoll Music
        - Rodgers, Michael - I like it like that, 1988; SR-29705; Rodgers, Michael (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29706. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PAS 1293; A-side Matrix # XSS 1293A-1A
        - Rodgers, Michael - I like it like that, 1988; SR-29706; Rodgers, Michael (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29705. 2 copies.
        - Rodney O - These are my beats, 1986; SR-29707; Rodney O (Box 416)
          Catalog # DMSR 00668; A-side Matrix # DMSR 00668
          Egyptian Empire Records
        - Rodway - Don't stop trying, 1982; SR-29708; Rodway (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29709. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JD-13112; A-side Matrix # YD-13112-CCC 2-RCA
          Millennium
        - Rodway - Don't stop trying, 1982; SR-29709; Rodway (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29708. 2 copies.
        - Roger - If you're serious, 1987; SR-29710; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # 0-21072; A-side Matrix # 0-21072-A-SH1 B-32951 22487 1-1
        - Roger - Thrill seekers, 1987; SR-29711; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # 0-20866; A-side Matrix # 0-20866-A-SH1 B-30145-SH1 19347 1-1
        - Roger - Unlimited!, 1987; SR-29712; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # 1-25496; A-side Matrix # 1-25496 -A-SH 1 B-28619-SH1 17695 1-1 8587TD
        - Roger - (Everybody) get up, 1991; SR-29713; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # 0-40259; A-side Matrix # 0-40259-A-SR-1
        - Roger - Girl, cut it out, 1984; SR-29714; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # 0-20276; A-side Matrix # B-20434-SH1 SLM 8460 1-1 0-20276-A-SH1
        - Roger - Girl, cut it out, 1984; SR-29715; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
        - Roger - The saga continues…, 1984; SR-29716; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # 1-23975; A-side Matrix # B-19276-SH2 SLM 6588 1-3
        - Roger - I heard it through the grapevine; So ruff, so tuff, 1981; SR-29726; Roger; Troutman, Roger (Box 416)
          Catalog # PRO-A-974; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-974-A1 B-16010
        - Roger & Zapp - Living for the city, 1996; SR-29717; Roger & Zapp (Box 416)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8496; A-side Matrix # 0-43771/PRO-A-8496-A REI
        - Rogers, DeWane - The message is still the same, 1980; SR-29718; Rogers, DeWane; D.J. Rogers (Box 416)
          Catalog # JC 36376; A-side Matrix # PAL36376-1H K
          ARC
        - Rogers, Evan - Call my heart your home, 1989; SR-29719; Rogers, Evan (Box 416)
          Catalog # V-15449; A-side Matrix # V-1-15449 -Z1 -DMM SPI-2
        - Roger S. - Strictly 4 the underground (Disc one), 1995; SR-29720; Roger S. (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29721. Double album.
          Catalog # SR EP9; A-side Matrix # SR-EP-9-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 12220
        - Roger S. - Strictly 4 the underground (Disc two), 1995; SR-29721; Roger S. (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29720. Double album.
          Catalog # SR EP9; A-side Matrix # SR-EP-9-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 12220
        - Roger S. - Livin 4 the underground, 1995; SR-29722; Roger S. (Box 416)
          Catalog # SR12377; A-side Matrix # SR-12377-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 12222
        - Rok - Silky, 1998; SR-29727; Rok (Box 416)
          Catalog # 74321 63110 1; A-side Matrix # B818778-01 A1
        - Rok - Silky, 1998; SR-29728; Rok (Box 416)
        - Rok - Use me no. 1, 1998; SR-29729; Rok; Disko; Jonzon; Beroshima (Box 416)
          Catalog # MUELLER2017 A; A-side Matrix # Müller 2017
          Müller Records
        - Roland Rat Superstar - Rat rapping, 1983; SR-29730; Roland Rat Superstar (Box 416)
          Catalog # 12RAT 1; A-side Matrix # 12 RAT 1 A-2U-1-1-
          Rodent Records
          England
        - Roli Rho - Adobo breaks, 2001; SR-29731; Roli Rho (Box 416)
          Catalog # TT 004; A-side Matrix # TT0041 STH-A
          Tabletools
        - Roli Rho - Adobo breaks, 2001; SR-29732; Roli Rho (Box 416)
        - Rolle, Ralph - Roxanne's a man (the untold story - final chapter), 1985; SR-29733; Rolle, Ralph (Box 416)
          Catalog # SW-2239; A-side Matrix # SW-2239-A
        - Rolling Stones - Miss you, 2002; SR-29734; Rolling Stones (Box 416)
          Catalog # CBRK-003; A-side Matrix # CBRK-003 A
          Club Rockers
        - Rolling Stones - Rolled gold - the very best of the Rolling Stones (disc one), 1975; SR-29735; Rolling Stones (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29736. Double album.
          Catalog # Z/ARL 14077; A-side Matrix # ZARL 14 16 670 04 1 1 29
          Decca
        - Rolling Stones - Rolled gold - the very best of the Rolling Stones (disc two), 1975; SR-29736; Rolling Stones (Box 416)
          In same jacket as # SR-29735. Double album.
          Catalog # Z/ARL 14077; A-side Matrix # ZARL 14079 4X ED 112
        - Rolling Stones - Still life (American concert 1981), 1982; SR-29737; Rolling Stones (Box 416)
          Catalog # COC 39113; A-side Matrix # ST-RS-824925-B
          Rolling Stones Records
        - Rolling Stones - Miss you (special disco version), 1978; SR-29738; Rolling Stones (Box 416)
          Catalog # DK 4609; A-side Matrix # ST DSKO 35247-1
        - Rick & DJ Jimmie Jaz - Funky rappin', 1987; SR-30962; Rick & DJ Jimmie Jaz (Box 147)
          Catalog # PW 427; A-side Matrix # PW-427-A POW WOW
          Pow Wow Records
          Mold remediated.
        - Rita Mitsouko - Andy, 1987; SR-30963; Rita Mitsouko (Box 147)
          In same jacket as # SR-30964. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # DMD 1070; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-53093-53101-1
          Mold remediated, jacket stored separately from vinyl.
        - Rita Mitsouko - Andy, 1987; SR-30964; Rita Mitsouko (Box 147)
          In same jacket as # SR-30963. Multiple copies.